Hello friends, my name is
Gaurav and the name of the channel is Mention, friends today we will
talk about our
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company, it is a perfect for long term
investment, the size of bringing it today, the break
of break in it with good volume, there is
hope of subscription,
see this, when the scheduled market has
its IP, it had set it very well,
see how big a boom it gave to this
Dungar of farewell, after that it kept moving slowly,
today, yesterday's last
market, then there was a bell plant,
it tried to cross its all time high
and with good volume, a
very good golden cross happened in Remedy,
due to which it seems that such a boom you should
subscribe to it, Video Channel, this is a
perfect look for long term investment, those of you who
watch and follow my channel,
they know that I
always talk about 19, which is for long
term investment, I make decisions only after
looking at every parameter
and I always like 19, so
go for long term  That the long-range
smell is the effort that I have made
in the video, so I understand the business of the company,
subscribe, there is a rule below in everything
like we Ghaghra and subscribe,
business will grow in India too, you must be educated, at this
time subscribe to everything in India,
if you watch the video
often then this market is well penetrated
and this is the company which deals in this year,
before this I have talked about
HDFC Life Ready to Bond in the video before the stipulated period and
you see after making the video of HDFC Life, there is
1518% growth in it and even now
friend,
ICICI Lombard is also a
good company in the part of HDFC Life, it is a good departmental
company, its business model is perfect, I
understand, how does this business do business, how does
it make profit, how does it work,
how does its business run, what will happen if its customers
increase, everything is understood, the
thinking of this company is understood, we could understand it,
we were able to lift it patiently,
all the companies fell in the week and many companies
recovered quickly, that is this recovery  What is it, now it has been done
and now talk about it because now people will
understand what happens this year, one can
also say that make a compulsion that every
question is there, like there is a compulsion that every measure will
not come out, you
need to subscribe to the group seriously and
subscribe, one
cannot live in these countries, if so, then they are going to do it from their
medical
Pimpri pocket, which is a very
bad company, it is a very good
company with very good fundamentals, like
we hear that 15 years ago someone invested
so much money in TCS and so much money in the company,
invest accordingly and
subscribe, see, it is a miraculous company, a
miraculous company, which we
can take and fold, cover the company at that level
and gift it to our children,
children should do it, father should see something, like
we get our property from our parents, we get
their payment,
you give them this and
you will forget what property is,
what gold is, Mr. Rakesh
Jhunjhunwala says it is soil, the
reason is that he gives
them so much money towards property that  You can understand that
I have so many thousands of crores Kumar Jain Parsi
people animals wild company offers a wide range
general insurance product covering fire
I am talking about many such that instead of that
ICICI Bank is born but
their banks are opened at many places, they do
not need to go outside,
customers come to the bank and subscribe in large numbers, for
them this is a very big
market company worth 6 crores 500 500 I said
subscribe that it is trying to climb up
Aamir in that breakup an
excellent accused better officer watch my video
so a lot and this Parv Virvar which
tells about the company how the company is working how the
company makes money from its own money
subscribe button liquid which is the
equity portion of the company you put on it this you are
taking out some of the equity of the company from the total of the company
hello friends
our money has to be made from these parameters if these two parameters of a company are
good the quality of the company will be
good the
price will be good then we will make money
friends if this company is ok its business is
4 it has profit chapter note  How will the
company expand its business from that profit,
how will its price increase,
how will the market value of the company increase, that is where
your money will be made and then this company,
this company is earning money, you have to make your pick six,
we have not got anything,
we have to meet that which will increase the price of the company,
a backstreet company front, the
biggest thing is such a good company and such a big
business Singh and so much speed that the
fees of the film industry on reel printers,
that the tenth specific is running at a good level,
friends, one of the biggest things that I
find scary in these stocks is its
intrinsic value of 1521 and protein is getting 5110,
friend, such a big business, how
good is Bijnor, you are getting intrinsic value,
intense invalid, if you get a business, you should
grab it, such a business will be
bold, see this friends, Twenty-20 is worth 1995
crores, this time whose stitching is there,
in September, the health of 2854, see the good profit,
profit of 416, this time the profit was 318, the sub number
was 90, see good tips in comparison to June
Friends, this time here in
September 1950, 6.7 and the same time share all time
high profit golden back margin, let's see
that this time when I was studying,
which I found best, earlier its margin was
at 715, Team Recent Airtel 60, at this
time Prashant has maintained the margin at a maximum level,
he has
kept the marking in MP3, friends,
very good results, you see, which I show
you every time in the video,
98% case of growth was increasing since 10 years, there is
some time for the list and in 3 years its business has
increased by 6 sandwich, then read further,
profit Jainul profit 23 cents earlier
3901 still comeback 29 accused, see first
fifteen and at this time NC is falling,
CCR is visible 3006, any of your money has been made
in three years
and in 1 year 19, run, that is, bread, it will
run, its turn has come, its
number is now, friends, I am  I was
checking my portfolio to see which stocks were gone and which were
pending to switch off and run away. Then I
found that I had 50% off on my stop board.
Whatever tuitions were stopped, then Priyanka
Pandey department, stock in life, now this will run
well. Friends, the business model is
good. It seems to understand the business.
Keep a large holding in vouchers. The promoter has reduced the
DLF holding. A little luck,
friends. Look at its time profile. There are two
big actors. The money doubled in 3 years.
Thirteen rupees in 3 months and in six months, see through
ATM. Next three months,
I think this should run till 1000.
If the market does not tell anything, then at this
level, if good news comes, then no one knows
where it is.
Yes, yes, the technical pattern is very good. There is
no shortage in the stock today.
An excellent score for long term
investment. For long term old, this is a
live stock of your property. This is a
property in a posh area of ​​the city where you live.
Hold on to it from your ICICI Lombard General. Friends, it will
make a lot of money. You have made me very rich. Thank you.
Friends, see you in the next video.
Friends, please like the video and
subscribe to the channel and if you
need polish service, you can WhatsApp me on the number given below.
For polish service,
my husband has taken the report for the friend circle.
Now I have talked to the teams yesterday and will
make a great portfolio for all three of them. I will
talk to us also. If you
need portfolio service today, Saturday, you
can WhatsApp me. Your
report will be ready tomorrow. Thank you friends.
See you in the next video. Thank you Dhan.